Joshua Roth

McKinney, TX Phone: 214-504-6200 | Email: Raider4414@gmail.com

Summary

Front-end web developer currently training at the University of Texas coding boot camp and will earn my certificate in full-stack web development March 15th. I have spent the past three years as a contractor building and managing websites for clients using a CMS.

Technical Skills

Html, Css, Javascript, MySQL, Bootstrap, Git, NodeJS, express, Jquery, and handlebars.

Experience

Contractor/Web Designer Faithson Solutions

2020-2024

Sherman, TX

Design and develop websites using CMS. Communicate with the clients to bring their vision to life. Troubleshoot any bugs and fix them within a reasonable timeframe. Set deadlines on projects.

Key Accomplishments:

Designed and employed over 20 websites

Associate Pastor

2019-2020

Antioch Baptist Church

Lovelady, TX

Public speaking, organized events and managed technology.

Key Accomplishments:

Built and deployed their website

Senior Pastor

Pinkham Baptist Church

Lovelady, TX

Organized meetings over budget and leadership. Public speaking and help to build their first website.

Large Animal Help/Farm Hand Henderson Animal Care

2013-2017

2018-2019

Henderson, TX

Clean kennels, stalls and grounds. Help work cattle in a safe manner. Ran lawn equipment to keep the building and facilities presentable

Education

Program Certificate: University of Texas, Austin, TX In-progress (March 15th) A 16 week intensive Fullstack program focused on gaining skills in Html, Css and MERN Stack.

 $\textbf{Masters of Theology:} \ \mathsf{Texas} \ \mathsf{Baptist} \ \mathsf{Institute}, \ \mathsf{Henderson}, \ \mathsf{TX}$

2012-2019